FireDrum's Legal Privacy Policy | FireDrum Email Marketing                

* Solutions

Select Page

Privacy Policy
==============

FireDrum Internet Marketing LLC, the parent company of FireDrum, is committed to protecting your online privacy. Because FireDrum’s services focus on the collection and analysis of various types of information that our users voluntarily provide us, we recommend you read this Privacy Policy so you will understand how your personal information will be treated as you use our services. Please understand our commitment to meeting the demands of our users may result in changes or additions to this Privacy Policy. In the event of such a change, FireDrum will post the revised Privacy Policy to our web site so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms and Conditions of the use of our website. By using our website, you pledge to abide by those Terms and Conditions.

In our commitment to protecting the privacy of our website’s visitors and clients, we have created a secure online environment that gives you control of what you share with the rest of the FireDrum Community. We uphold the highest industry standards in online privacy and permission marketing. For more information on how FireDrum enforces permission email marketing with all our clients and affiliates, please see our Anti-Spam Policy.

The Information We Collect
--------------------------

Our registration forms require users to give us contact information that may include name, email address, address and facts about you and/or your company. We do not request sensitive information from our visitors, such as credit card or social security numbers, unless they are signing up and paying for our services. We never sell, share or trade any of our customer information with other companies.

How We Collect and Use Information from Contacts
------------------------------------------------

FireDrum.com gives contacts the opportunity to receive news, promotions and other information via email from their favorite companies. You will only receive these emails if you grant us or the company permission to communicate information to you. To successfully communicate a personalized message to you, you must subscribe by providing us or the company with your name and email address at the minimum.

### There are several ways to subscribe including:

Clicking a link on a company’s email that has been forwarded to you by the “Refer a Friend” option. We do not store your email address unless you join the Email List. We do not store your friend’s comments to you.

Clicking on any banner ad attached to an email message from an Email List you have already joined.  
Completing a form or following links on a company’s website to opt-in to their Email List.  
Providing your name and email address and granting consent to a company by other means.  
Once you enroll, we send you a confirmation email indicating the source of your subscription request with a link to unsubscribe if you elect not to remain a member.

When you join, your name, email address and any other general information you have voluntarily provided in your Contact Profile section are not shared.

If you join one or more Email Lists through one or more of the methods above, your information is owned separately by each company whose Email Lists you have joined. Moreover, FireDrum’s right to use your information to contact you independently, and not in conjunction with Email Lists sponsors, is more limited.

FireDrum does not share any of your personal information with third parties, other than sharing your profile information with the sponsoring establishment for each Email List you join. FireDrum may employ data entry firms or other vendors to assist in the entry and administration of member information and email transmissions. Any such vendors is subject to confidentiality agreements and do not have any right to use or disclose member information except in connection with their contracted services.

FireDrum does not collect any information about you other than your first name and email address unless you provide it voluntarily. Please note that you are under no obligation whatsoever to provide this extra personal information to continue to receive your periodic promotion and special event news. If you do provide FireDrum.com and your Email List sponsors with more in-depth personal interest information, we can highly personalize the communication and tailor it to your interests and needs.

Website Usage Information
-------------------------

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. We do not link your IP address to any personally identifiable information. We use tracking information to determine which areas our site users visit based on traffic to those areas. FireDrum does not track what individual users read, but rather how often each page is visited and helps us maintain a superior and informative website for you.

Your Email Lists and Databases
------------------------------

FireDrum and its parent company never sell, rent, share or otherwise make available your email lists or databases to anyone except internal support personnel who may be assisting you in troubleshooting your account. FireDrum is not in the business of selling data. FireDrum is in the business of providing web-based e-mail services.

Security and Privacy
--------------------

FireDrum’s website uses security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We store the information in our database within a secure environment at our data center. We never sell, rent or share individual personal information with anyone unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your subscriptions.

Permission Opt-In
-----------------

When subscribing to an email newsletter, our contacts and their subscribers are given the opportunity to ‘opt-in’ to having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site. Any outside parties will never collect users of our site. We do this to ensure that our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

Tracked Information
-------------------

On occasion, we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. We also may track browser types to help us understand our visitors’ needs as they relate to our website design. There is an optional section of our website where input forms require your name, company, and email address. This form provides the ability to opt-in to receiving future emails of any kind from FireDrum. If you opt-in to receiving email communications from us, then we may send information to you on our products or services. You may review and change your information at any time by clicking on the “modify profile” link found at the bottom of emails sent via our system, or by contacting us.

Security Technology
-------------------

FireDrum has made a substantial investment in the latest server, database, backup and firewall technologies to protect our information assets. These technologies are deployed as part of sophisticated security architecture. All data resides in a tightly controlled, secure data center. These investments ensure information about the identity and preferences of individual contacts is never accessible to anyone outside of FireDrum. We maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information.

Cookies and Why We Use Them
---------------------------

We maintain all data for tracking a user’s session on our server. A cookie is a small data file that a website transfers to a user’s hard drive when the user visits the website. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the website uses to track pages visited. The only personal information a cookie can contain is what the user supplies. A cookie cannot read data off a hard drive or read cookie files created by other websites. Many internet services deliver cookies to visitors, but we do not. Cookies store information about your use on your computer where the same service can only retrieve it at a later time. Cookies are used by internet companies to make their services more convenient and personalized. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but by modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set or to reject all cookies. You can also delete cookies from your hard drive.

Links to Other Sites
--------------------

Please note that while our website contains links to other sites, the privacy policy of these other sites is likely not identical to our own. Merchants who sponsor an Email List we support may maintain their privacy policy. We encourage you to pay attention to when you leave our website and to investigate and ask questions before disclosing any information to other sites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the information collected by FireDrum.com.

Access to Google User Data
--------------------------

Within the FireDrum service, you may login with your Google account to upload files to the service from your Google Drive. We will not store any data received from Google other than the selected files, should you choose any, in the Google Drive file selection screen.

Acquisition or Changes in Ownership of FireDrum
-----------------------------------------------

If FireDrum (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, customer information would be considered part of those assets and may be part of those assets that are transferred.

Policy Modifications
--------------------

FireDrum notifies its contacts and users via email if we make any changes to our Privacy Policy. Any new policy is posted on our site at least one week before going into effect. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we notify users through email. Users have a choice as to whether or not we use their information differently.

FireDrum Internet Marketing LLC dba FireDrum. All Rights Reserved. Other trademarks and service marks used herein are the property of their respective owners.

A software you can get behind.
==============================

Since 2001, our permission-based email marketing service combines an easy-to-use application with industry best personal support. At FireDrum, we do not believe in a one size fits all solution. Learn more by reading real client reviews and testimonials on Capterra.

FireDrum is an email marketing service. We offer a variety of solutions that fit in every budget and support unique needs. Whether you want to do it yourself or have us manage your email campaigns, will be here to help.

**SALES**  [(480) 699-1524](tel:4806991524)

**SUPPORT**  [support@firedrum.com](mailto:support@firedrum.com)

Company

Resources

More Solutions

Yes, send me tips on email marketing!
-------------------------------------

FireDrum will never share your information.

Sign Up

You have Successfully Subscribed!
---------------------------------

Receive free marketing advice and stay informed.
------------------------------------------------

Submit

We look forward to speaking with you!
-------------------------------------

Your identity is safe with FireDrum. We will never share your contact information.

Join Our Newsletter
